const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Who do you play in the main games?',
        answer1: 'Zelda',
        answer2: 'Tingle',
        answer3: 'Skull Kid',
        answer4: 'Link',
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the TriForce?',
        answer1: 'The power of the Golden Goddesses',
        answer2: 'Tattoo for members of the Yiga Clan',
        answer3: 'The instrument Link plays music with',
        answer4: 'A powerful finishing move',
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the usual main antagonist?',
        answer1: 'Zant',
        answer2: 'King of Red Lions',
        answer3: 'Majora',
        answer4: 'Ganon',
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: 'What does each piece of the TriForce stand for?',
        answer1: 'Cool, Calm, and Collected',
        answer2: 'Water, Fire, and Grass',
        answer3: 'Power, Wisdom, and Courage',
        answer4: 'Love, Peace, and Tranquility',
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'Who created the Legend of Zelda?',
        answer1: 'Shigeru Miyamoto',
        answer2: 'Chuck Norris',
        answer3: 'Shigeki Morimoto',
        answer4: 'Koji Okada',
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Zelda\'s alter ego in Ocarina of Time?',
        answer1: 'Impa',
        answer2: 'Sheik',
        answer3: 'Tetra',
        answer4: 'Saria',
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: 'When was the first Legend of Zelda originally released?',
        answer1: '1986',
        answer2: '1982',
        answer3: '1985',
        answer4: '1990',
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the games is set in the span of 3 days?',
        answer1: 'Wind Waker',
        answer2: 'Link\s Awakening',
        answer3: 'Majora\'s Mask',
        answer4: 'Minish Cap',
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the games main plot involves time travel?',
        answer1: 'Skyward Sword',
        answer2: 'Twilight Princess',
        answer3: 'The Adventure of Link',
        answer4: 'Ocarina of Time',
        correctAnswer:4,
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the best selling Legend of Zelda game?',
        answer1: 'Ocarina of Time',
        answer2: 'Legend of Zelda (the Original)',
        answer3: 'Breath of the Wild',
        answer4: 'Phantom Hourglass',
        correctAnswer: 3,
    }
];
